module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Gin and tonics are a fun way to prevent what disease?', 
    a: 'Malaria',
    b: 'Giardia',
    c: 'Sobriety',
    d: 'Rickets',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'The fictional "Three Laws of Robotics" were created by:', 
    a: 'Le Guin',
    b: 'Bradbury',
    c: 'Asimov',
    d: 'Bender',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many tablespoons in a quarter cup?', 
    a: '2.5',
    b: '3',
    c: '4',
    d: '1.2 billion',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In a normal environment, a human can survive for ___ days without water. ', 
    a: '1',
    b: '3-5',
    c: '11-15',
    d: 'up to 21',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'In hunting, the number of points a buck is worth is determined by its:', 
    a: 'Weight',
    b: 'Shoulder Height',
    c: 'Shirt Size',
    d: 'Horns',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Buddhism originated in what is now:', 
    a: 'India',
    b: 'China',
    c: 'Japan',
    d: 'Your Mom',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Sister Rosetta Tharpe basically invented:', 
    a: 'Nunnery',
    b: 'Ski-dancing',
    c: 'Rock n\' Roll',
    d: 'Rollerblades',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Rogaine was originally developed as a medication for:', 
    a: 'Erectile Dysfunction',
    b: 'Blood Pressure',
    c: 'High Cholesterol',
    d: 'Jock Itch',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The northern lights are caused by:', 
    a: 'Sound Waves',
    b: 'Chemtrails',
    c: 'Hundreds of Bees',
    d: 'Solar Flares',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In Calvin and Hobbes, what was Calvin\'s main super hero alter ego?', 
    a: 'Underpants Man',
    b: 'Zorcher',
    c: 'King Dino',
    d: 'Spaceman Spiff',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];